BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VIII: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
  - Code no.6903: Service Stations and IBT Local 705, 1959-1970 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Service Stations and IBT Local 705, 1959-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 26)
      Agreement effective 08/01/1959 and expires on 04/30/1962. Covers 6000 workers in Chicago, IL.
    - Item 2: Service Stations and IBT Local 705, 1962-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 26)
      Agreement effective 11/01/1962 and expires on 10/31/1963. Covers 6000 workers in Chicago, IL.
    - Item 3: Service Stations and IBT Local 705, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 26)
      Agreement effective 11/01/1964 and expires on 10/31/1967. Covers 6000 workers in Chicago, IL.
    - Item 4: Service Stations and IBT Local 705, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 26)
      Agreement effective 11/01/1967 and expires on 10/31/1970. Covers 6000 workers in Chicago, IL.
  - Code no.6902: Greater St. Louis Automotive Association and IAM District 9, 1959-1970 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Greater St. Louis Automotive Association and IAM District 9, 1959-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 08/01/1959 and expires on 07/31/1964. Covers 1200 workers in St. Louis, MO.
    - Item 2: Greater St. Louis Automotive Association and IAM District 9, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 08/01/1964 and expires on 07/31/1967. Covers 2000 workers in St. Louis, MO.
    - Item 3: Greater St. Louis Automotive Association and IAM District 9, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 08/01/1967 and expires on 07/31/1970. Covers 1400 workers in St. Louis, MO.
  - Code no.6901: Automotive Repair Industry of San Mateo County and IAM Local 1414, 1958-1965 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Automotive Repair Industry of San Mateo County and IAM Local 1414, 1958-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 07/15/1958 and expires on 07/16/1961. Covers 1200 workers in San Mateo, CA; Santa Clara, CA.
    - Item 2: Automotive Repair Industry of San Mateo County and IAM Local 1414, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 09/18/1961 and expires on 07/16/1963. Covers 1200 workers in San Mateo, CA; Santa Clara, CA.
    - Item 3: Code no.6901: Automotive Repair Industry of San Mateo County and IAM Local 1414, 1961-1963 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Item 4: Automotive Repair Industry of San Mateo County and IAM Local 1414, 1963-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 07/15/1963 and expires on 07/16/1965. Covers 1300 workers in San Mateo, CA; Santa Clara, CA.
    - Item 5: Code no.6901: Automotive Repair Industry of San Mateo County and IAM Local 1414, 1963-1965 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Code no.6832: Safeway Stores, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Association Local 368, 1962-1967 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: Safeway Stores, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Association Local 368, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 29)
      Agreement effective 03/09/1962 and expires on 02/03/1964. Covers 300 workers in Fort Worth, TX; Arlington, TX.
    - Item 2: Safeway Stores, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Association Local 368, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 29)
      Agreement effective 02/04/1964 and expires on 02/04/1967. Covers 300 workers in Fort Worth, TX; Arlington, TX.
  - Code no.6805: Giant Food Inc. and Retail Store Employees' Union Local 692, 1969-1973 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: Giant Food Inc. and Retail Store Employees' Union Local 692, 1969-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 30)
      Agreement effective 07/20/1969 and expires on 07/17/1971. Covers 1500 workers in Baltimore, MD.
    - Item 2: Giant Food Inc. and Retail Store Employees' Union Local 692, 1971-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 30)
      Agreement effective 07/18/1971 and expires on 08/26/1972. Covers 1650 workers in Baltimore, MD.
    - Item 3: Giant Food Inc. and Retail Store Employees' Union Local 692, 1972-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 30)
      Agreement effective 08/27/1972 and expires on 08/25/1973. Covers 1800 workers in Baltimore, MD.
  - Code no.6804: Vornado Corp. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 1262, 1963-1970 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: Vornado Corp. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 1262, 1963-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 31)
      Agreement effective 01/01/1963 and expires on 12/31/1965. Covers 4000 workers in New York, NY; NJ.
    - Item 2: Vornado Corp. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 1262, 1965-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 31)
      Agreement effective 05/30/1965 and expires on 05/29/1970. Covers 4000 workers in New York, NY; NJ.
  - Code no.6801: National Tea Co. and Retail Clerks Local Unions 725, 25, 1441, 550, 1967-1970 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: National Tea Co. and Retail Clerks Local Unions 725, 25, 1441, 550, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 32)
      Agreement effective 02/27/1967 and expires on 03/01/1970. Covers 1300 workers in Marion, IN.
  - Code no.6792: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Locals 135, 200, 270, 337, 371, 383, 435, 544, 610, 688, 738, 984, 1963-1970 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1965-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 01/01/1965 and expires on 06/01/1967. Covers 1285 workers in Washington, DC.
    - Item 2: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1963-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 10/14/1963 and expires on 12/31/1968. Covers 40 workers in St. Louis, MO.
    - Item 3: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 06/01/1964 and expires on 05/31/1967. Covers 218 workers in Minneapolis, MN.
    - Item 4: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Item 5: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1963-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 09/12/1963 and expires on 06/04/1967. Covers 1285 workers.
    - Item 6: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1964-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 09/12/1964 and expires on 09/11/1968. Covers 120 workers.
    - Item 7: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1963-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Item 8: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 09/06/1964 and expires on 09/02/1967. Covers 165 workers in Indianapolis, IN.
    - Item 9: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Item 10: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Item 11: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 02/03/1964 and expires on 06/04/1967. Covers 550 workers in Chicago, IL.
    - Item 12: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 02/25/1963 and expires on 02/27/1966. Covers 161 workers in New Orleans, LA.
    - Item 13: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 01/14/1963 and expires on 01/16/1966. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Memphis, TN.
    - Item 14: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1964-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 01/01/1964 and expires on 12/31/1966. Covers 35 workers in St. Louis, MO.
    - Item 15: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 05/24/1964 and expires on 06/04/1967. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Detroit, MI.
    - Item 16: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 04/05/1964 and expires on 04/01/1967. Covers 45 workers in Lavenport, IA.
    - Item 17: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 04/05/1964 and expires on 06/03/1967. Covers 160 workers in Milwaukee, WI.
    - Item 18: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 02/01/1964 and expires on 03/31/1967. Covers 160 workers in Milwaukee, WI.
    - Item 19: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1966-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 02/28/1966 and expires on 06/04/1967. Covers unknown number of workers workers in New Orleans, LA.
    - Item 20: National Tea Co. and National Warehouse Division of Teamsters Local, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 06/05/1967 and expires on 06/04/1970. Covers unknown number of workers workers.
  - Code no.6791: J. Weingarten Inc. and Retail Clerks International Association Local 455, 1968-1971 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: J. Weingarten Inc. and Retail Clerks International Association Local 455, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 34)
      Agreement effective 03/08/1965 and expires on 03/10/1968. Covers 3000 workers in Houston, TX.
  - Code no.6790: Independent Markets and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 196, 1964-1973 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: Independent Markets and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 196, 1964-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 35)
      Agreement effective 05/01/1964 and expires on 04/30/1966. Covers 1000 workers in Philadelphia, PA.
    - Item 2: Independent Markets and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 196, 1964-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Item 3: Independent Markets and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 196, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 35)
      Agreement effective 05/01/1966 and expires on 05/01/1969. Covers 1000 workers in Philadelphia, PA.
    - Item 4: Independent Markets and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 196, 1969-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 35)
      Agreement effective 05/01/1969 and expires on 04/30/1971. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Philadelphia, PA.
    - Item 5: Independent Markets and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 196, 1971-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 35)
      Agreement effective 05/01/1971 and expires on 04/30/1973. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Philadelphia, PA.
- Series IX: Industry Code #45, Retail Trade
  - Code no.6502: Federal Department Stores, Inc. and Central States Joint Board, Retail and Department Store Employees Local 362, 1959- 1968 (Box 23, Folder 6502)
  - Code no.6504: Gimbel's and United Department Store Workers Local 2, 1963-1968 (Box 23, Folder 6504)
  - Code no.6508: Macy's New York and Retail, Wholesale, Department Store Workers Local 1-S, 1961-1970 (Box 23, Folder 6508)
- Series X: Industry Code #48, Transportation and Warehousing
  - Code no.5009: D.C. Transit System, Inc. and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees Local 689, 1959-1965 (Box 14, Folder 5009)
  - Code no.5015: Milwaukee and Suburban Transport corporation and Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 998, 1963-1970 (Box 14, Folder 5015)
  - Code no.5022: Public Service Coordinated Transport and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees Locals 819, 820, 821, 822, 823, 824, 825, 880, 947, 1960-1970 (Box 14, Folder 5022)
  - Code no.5029: Yellow Cab Company of Philadelphia and IBT Local 156, 1961-1963 (Box 14, Folder 5029)
  - Code no.5033: Eastern Greyhound Lines and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees, 1962- 1966 (Box 14, Folder 5033)
  - Code no.5037: Central Greyhound Lines and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees Locals 1126, 1150, 1313, 1962-1966 (Box 15, Folder 5037)
  - Code no.5200: California Trucking Association, Inc. and IBT Locals 70, 85, 287, 315, 490, 624, 890, 912, 980, 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 5200)
  - Code no.5211: Carolina Freight Council and IBT Local 71, 391, 61, 509, 1955-1970 (Box 15, Folder 5211)
  - Code no.5212: Carolina Freight Council and IBT Eastern Conference, 1955-1970 (Box 15, Folder 5212)
- Code no.6753: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council Locals 1349, 1357, 1358, 1360, 1361, 1371, 1393, 1959-1970 (Box 36, Folder 6753)
- Code no.6753: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. and Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council Locals 1349, 1357, 1358, 1360, 1361, 1371, 1393, 1959-1970 (Box 36, Folder 6753)
  - Code no.5213: Central States Area Over-the-Road Freight Assoc. and IBT, 1961-1967 (Box 15, Folder 5213)
  - Code no.5214: Central States Area Cartage Agreement and Employees of Private, Common, Contract and Local Cartage Carriers, 1961- 1967 (Box 15, Folder 5214)
  - Code no.5215: New York-New Jersey Area General Trucking Agreement and New York-New Jersey Area Freight Council, 1960- 1964 (Box 15, Folder 5215)
  - Code no.5216: N/A and IBT, 1961-1967 (Box 15, Folder 5216)
  - Code no.5217: Moving and Storages Industry of New York, NY and IBT Local 814, 1959-1968 (Box 15, Folder 5217)
  - Code no.5218: Petroleum Companies of Minnesota and IBT Central Conference, 1957-1967 (Box 15, Folder 5218)
  - Code no.5219: Trucking-Local Cartage and IBT Local 705, 1961-1967 (Box 15, Folder 5219)
  - Code no.5220: Dallas, TX Trucking Companies and Union of Transportation Employees, Charter 102870, 1962-1969 (Box 15, Folder 5220)
  - Code no.5222: Chicago Trucking Companies and Chicago Truck Drivers Local 705, 1961-1967 (Box 15, Folder 5222)
  - Code no.5223: Portland, Maine Trucking Companies and Truck Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers Union Local 340, 1961- 1970 (Box 15, Folder 5223)
  - Code no.5224: New England Freight Agreement and IBT, 1961-1967 (Box 15, Folder 5224)
  - Code no.5239: Drayage and Household Moving Agreement and Truck Owners' Association of Seattle, Inc., 1961-1967 (Box 15, Folder 5239)
- Code no.6771: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Locals 56, 195, 198, 199, 1959- 1971 (Box 36, Folder 6771)
  - Code no.5249: National Master Freight Agreement and Maryland-District of Columbia Freight Council, 1961-1970 (Box 15, Folder 5249)
- Code no.6771: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Locals 56, 195, 198, 199, 1959- 1971 (Box 36, Folder 6771)
  - Code no.5247: Western Truck Lines and Western States Longhaul Common Carriers, 1962-1968 (Box 15, Folder 5247)
  - Code no.5248: National Master Freight Agreement and Central Pennsylvania Motor Carriers, 1962-1973 (Box 15, Folder 5248)
  - Code no.5251: National Master Freight Agreement and Tri-Area Labor Association and Independent Associations, Philadelphia and Vicinity, 1964-1970 (Box 15, Folder 5251)
  - Code no.5263: National Master Freight Agreement and Western States Area Over-the-Road, 1964-1967 (Box 15, Folder 5263)
  - Code no. 5265: California Trucking Association and National Master Freight Agreement and Western States Area Office Employees, 1964- 1967 (Box 15, Folder 5265)
  - Code no.5272: Cement Agreement and IBT Central and Southern Conference, 1960-1964 (Box 15, Folder 5272)
  - Code no.5400: Atlantic and Gulf District Standard Tanker Agreement and National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association, 1958- 1965 (Box 16, Folder 5400)
  - Code no.5401: Committee for Companies and Agents, Atlantic and Gulf Coasts and National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association, 1960-1969 (Box 16, Folder 5401)
  - Code no. 5402: Various Companies and Agents (Atlantic and Gulf Coasts) and the National Maritime Union of America, AFL-CIO, 1961- 1969 (Box 16, Folder 5402)
  - Code no.5403: Dry Cargo and Passenger Companies and International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots, 1958-1961 (Box 16, Folder 5403)
  - Code no. 5404: Moore-McCormack Lines, Inc. and Seafarers International Union of North America - Atlantic, Gulf, Lakes and Inland Waters District, AFL-CIO, 1965-1968 (Box 16, Folder 5404)
  - Code no.5405: American Maritime Association and Seafarers International Union of North America-Atlantic, Gulf, Lakes and Inland Waters District, 1960-1972 (Box 16, Folder 5405)
  - Code no.5410: Pacific Maritime Association and International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots Local 90, 1958-1965 (Box 16, Folder 5410)
- Code no.6789: Frederick's Markets and Retail Clerks International Association Local 1625, 1963-1966 (Box 36, Folder 6789)
  - Code no.5411: Pacific Maritime Association and West Coast Ship Operators, 1950-1969 (Box 16, Folder 5411)
  - Code no.5413: Pittsburgh Steamship Division, U.S. Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 16, Folder 5413)
  - Code no.5423: New York Shipping Association, Inc. and International Longshoremen's Association, 1956-1959 (Box 17, Folder 5423)
  - Code no.5002: Baltimore Transit Company and Amalgamated Association of Street Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees Local 1300, 1960-1965 (Box 33, Folder 5002)
  - Code no.5029: Yellow Cab Co. of Philadelphia and Taxicab Drivers Union Local 156, 1965-1969 (Box 33, Folder 5029)
  - Code no.5030: Yellow Cab Co. of Los Angeles and IBT Local 640, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 5030)
  - Code no.5041: Taxi Cab Drivers of New York and New York City Taxi Drivers Union Local 3036, 1967-1969 (Box 33, Folder 5041)
  - Code no.5200: California Trucking Association, Inc. and Pickup and Delivery Locals 70, 890, 287, 7, 490, 1967-1970 (Box 33, Folder 5200)
  - Code no.5201: California Trucking Association, Inc. and IAM Locals 41, 87, 93, 95, 138, 164, 1962-1965 (Box 33, Folder 5201)
  - Code no.5205: Cartage Exchange of Chicago, Inc. and Automobile Mechanics' Local 701, 1961-1967 (Box 33, Folder 5205)
  - Code no.5208: Empire State Highway Transportation Association and IBT Local 607, 1960-1964 (Box 33, Folder 5208)
  - Code no.5209: Western and Central Conference Area Supplemental Agreements and IBT, 1961-1967 (Box 33, Folder 5209)
  - Code no.5221: Office and Miscellaneous Truck Terminal Employers and IBT Local 710, 1961-1970 (Box 33, Folder 5221)
- Series XI: Industry Code #49, Transportation and Warehousing
  - Code no.5240: United Parcel Service of New York, Inc. and IBT Locals 138, 177, 478, 804, 1959-1965 (Box 15, Folder 5240)
  - Code no.5249: United Parcel Service and IBT Locals 186, 381, 396, 467, 542, 572, 871, 898, 952, 982, 1964-1966 (Box 15, Folder 5249)
  - Code no.5260: United Parcel Service and IBT, 1964-1970 (Box 15, Folder 5260)
- Series XII: Industry Code #51, Information
  - Code no.1402: Boston Daily Newspapers and Boston Typographical Union Local 13, 1961-1966 (Box 5, Folder 1402)
  - Code no.5700: American Telephone and Telegraph Company, Long Lines Company and CWA, 1960-1967 (Box 17, Folder 5700)
  - Code no.5703: Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania and Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1960-1966 (Box 17, Folder 5703)
  - Code no.5707: Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company and CWA, 1960-1963 (Box 17, Folder 5707)
  - Code no.5715: General Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and IBEW Locals 1635, 1636, 1637, 1960-1968 (Box 17, Folder 5715)
  - Code no.5716: Peninsular Telephone Company and IBEW, 1957-1973 (Box 17, Folder 5716)
  - Code no.5717: General Telephone Co. of Indiana and CWA, 1961-1967 (Box 17, Folder 5717)
  - Code no.5718: General Telephone Company of Wisconsin and CWA, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 5718)
  - Code no.5719: General Telephone Company of the Southwest and CWA, 1961-1968 (Box 17, Folder 5719)
  - Code no.5722: Illinois Bell Telephone Company and CWA, 1960-1965 (Box 17, Folder 5722)
  - Code no.5723: Illinois Bell Telephone Company and CWA Local 5016, 1961-1971 (Box 17, Folder 5723)
  - Code no.5728: Indiana Bell Telephone Company, Inc. and CWA, 1960-1966 (Box 17, Folder 5728)
  - Code no.5729: Indiana Bell Telephone Company, Inc. and CWA Traffic Dept. Bargaining Unit, 1963-1970 (Box 17, Folder 5729)
  - Code no.5730: Lincoln Telephone and Telegraph Company and CWA, 1959-1970 (Box 17, Folder 5730)
  - Code no.5732: Michigan Bell Telephone Company and CWA, 1960-1966 (Box 17, Folder 5732)
  - Code no.5734: Mountain States Telephone and Telegraph Company and CWA, 1960-1971 (Box 18, Folder 5734)
  - Code no.5735: Mountain States Telephone and Telegraph Company, Plant Department and CWA, 1960-1970 (Box 18, Folder 5735)
  - Code no.5736: New England Telephone and Telegraph Company and New England Federation of Telephone and Traffic Workers, 1959- 1969 (Box 18, Folder 5736)
  - Code no.5740: New Jersey Bell Telephone Company and Telephone Workers Union Local 827, 1963-1969 (Box 18, Folder 5740)
  - Code no.5742: Northwestern Bell Telephone Company and CWA, 1960-1969 (Box 18, Folder 5742)
  - Code no.5743: New York Telephone Company and Telephone Traffic Union of Upstate New York, 1960-1970 (Box 18, Folder 5743)
  - Code no.5745: New York Telephone Company and Telephone Employees' Organization--Accounting, 1963-1968 (Box 18, Folder 5745)
  - Code no.5748: New York Telephone Company and CWA, 1964-1971 (Box 18, Folder 5749)
  - Code no.5749: Empire City Subway Company and CWA, 1964-1971 (Box 18, Folder 5749)
  - Code no.5750: Ohio Bell Telephone Company and CWA, 1960-1966 (Box 18, Folder 5750)
  - Code no.5751: Bell Telephone Company of Nevada and IBEW Local 1011, 1961-1969 (Box 18, Folder 5751)
  - Code no.5752: Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Company and CWA, 1960-1971 (Box 18, Folder 5752)
  - Code no.5752: Bell Telephone Company of Nevada and CWA, 1960-1971 (Box 18, Folder 5752)
  - Code no.5753: Pacific Telephone-Northwest and CWA, 1960-1971 (Box 19, Folder 5753)
  - Code no. 5754: Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Company; Bell Telephone Company of Nevada and Communications Workers of America, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 5754)
  - Code no.5755: Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Company, Los Angeles Area and CWA, 1962-1969 (Box 19, Folder 5755)